RG 074:072, Joan Gilbert Tatro Genealogical Papers
Connecticut State Library
Joan Gilbert Tatro genealogical papers
1979-2012
Connecticut State Library
Tatro, Joan Gilbert
2 cubic feet
Contains notes, correspondence, photocopies of genealogical works, and miscellaneous genealogical research on various families. There are also a variety of genealogical newsletters concentrating on different families.
RG074_072
2012-056
Scope and Content
Contains notes, correspondence, photocopies of genealogical works, and miscellaneous genealogical research on various families. There are also a variety of genealogical newsletters concentrating on different families.
Arrangement
Series 1. Family Files, 1979-2007
Series 2. Photocopies, undated
Series 3. Newsletters, 1983-2012
Series 4. Photographs, undated
Series 5. Oversize Materials, undated
Index Terms
Family Names:
Baker family; Barker family; Beisiegel family; Bingham family; Bishop family; Blake family; Bush family; Cairns family; Chadbourne family; Clark family; Ellis family; Fitch family; Flagon family; Frisby family; Gilbert family; Gifford family; Givens family; Grafton family; Hale family; Helme family; Hepburn family; Hotchkiss family; Hubbell family; Hull family; Lobdell family; McCready family; Mitchell family; Moulthrope family; Mulvey family; Pease family; Palmer family; Perkins family; Phelps family; Pitcher family; Prior family; Rouse family; Rudd family; Sackett family; Schwarzwelder family; Swartzweller family; Smith family; Strong family; Sylvester family; Tatro family; Titus family; Tolman family; Topps family; Trencher family; Wells family; Williams family; Windsor family
Places:
Connecticut -- Genealogy; Massachusetts -- Genealogy
Document Types:
Correspondence; Genealogies; Newsletters; Photocopies; Photographs
Restrictions on Access
These papers are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Provenance
The papers came to the Connecticut State Library on June 25, 2012 from Joan Gilbert Tatro.
Container List
- Series 1. Family Files, 1979-2007
  - Bailey (Box 1)
  - Baker (Box 1)
  - Barker (Box 1)
  - Beisiegel/Schwarzwelder (Box 1)
  - Bingham/Rudd (Box 1)
  - Bishop (Box 1)
  - Bush (Box 1)
  - Cairns (Box 1)
  - Ellis (Box 1)
  - Fitch/Strong (Box 1)
  - Flagon/Trencher (Box 1)
  - Frisby (Box 1)
  - Gilbert - Estelle, Samuel and others (Box 1)
  - Gilbert/Perkins/Mulvey (Box 1)
  - Gilbert - Prudence and Sarah (Box 1)
  - Gifford (Box 1)
  - Grafton (Box 1)
  - Hale/Barker/Beisiegel/Swartzweller (Box 1)
  - Helme/Rouse (Box 1)
  - Hepburn/Clark (Box 1)
  - Hubbell (Box 1)
  - McCready - main file (Box 1)
  - McCready - odds and ends (Box 1)
  - Mitchell (Box 1)
  - Palmer (Box 1)
  - Pease/Prior (Box 1)
  - Phelps (Box 1)
  - Pitcher/Blake (Box 1)
  - Sackett (Box 2)
  - Smith (Box 2)
  - Smith - Stoughton and Canton MA (Box 2)
  - Sylvester (Box 2)
  - Tatro (Box 2)
  - Titus (Box 2)
  - Tolman/Givens (Box 2)
  - Topps (Box 2)
  - Wells (Box 2)
  - Williams/Moulthrope (Box 2)
  - Windsor (Box 2)
- Series 2. Photocopies, undated
  - Photocopies (Box 2)
  - Sheets not my family (Box 2)
- Series 3. Newsletters, 1983-2012
  - DAR Magazine (Box 2)
    - Corrections to Patriot Index, 1983 October-1988 October (Box 2)
    - More Genealogy, 1983 August-1989 May (Box 2)
    - New Ancestor Rewards, 1984 October 10 (Box 2)
  - Descendants of the Founders of Ancient Windsor Newsletter, 1983-1993, undated (Box 2)
  - Flagon & Trencher News, 2009 February-2011 March (Box 2)
  - GSS Newsletter, 1997 October-November (Box 2)
    The newsletter for the Genealogical Society of Sarasota in Florida.
  - Hotchkiss Family News, 1995 August, 2007 February-2012 May (Box 2)
  - Hull Family Association Journal, 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Hull Family Association Newsletter, 1992 March-1994 December (Box 2)
  - The Lobdell Lines Newsletter, 1988 August-1995 March (Box 2)
  - The Mary & John Cleaning House Newsletter, 1991-1995, undated (Box 2)
  - The Pied Cow: The Chadbourne Family Association Newsletter, 1999 Winter-2000 Summer (Box 2)
  - Windsor Historical Society News, 1984 June (Box 2)
- Series 4. Photographs, undated
  - Frances Hubbell Barker with Charles A. Barker, 1 envelope (Box 2)
- Series 5. Oversize Materials, undated; 1 envelope
  - Certificate of appreciation of service (Box Item 3)
    Given to Joan Tatro from the Suffield Woman's Club.
  - Map of Hartford (Box Item 3)
  - Map of New Haven (Box Item 3)
  - Photocopies of photographs (Box Item 3)